I love it so much, I love it so much, I hate it so much, I love it so much, I love it so much, I love it so much, I love it so much
Good morning.
A little spin on the wheel today, meat.
My posture is not so bad because my bangs are smooth since I got covered at the same time as the bullet train.
Sorry.
Good morning.
I guess yesterday, everyone was campaigning to get in the front of the line.
I asked to be the first one in today.
Wow, what a lot of sesherin again.
I had a hagi moon and some zunda cakes like this one just now.
Here's a kick hook.
I had bought some at my old house.
Frozen mappel daifuku.
Cheese balls.
Yes, yes, yes, they're famous for their sasa-kamaboko.
We had sasakamaboko for breakfast today, too!
Yay!
Let's eat!
Bye bye!
Ponkichi, got it!
Ghetto!
Cheese ball star shaped!
Good morning!
Today's hairstyle is a big bun!
Yay!
We are here in Sendai style Sendai!
Speaking of Sendai, it's a head thumbs up.
I'm going to try a lot of left eye winks today!
Yay!
And everyone
Are you listening to the cute memorial?
From today's Sendai performance, I'll be performing it in your ears.
Yes, and if you all thought I was a bit of a Jenga-player in the last episode...
If you thought for even a millimeter that I didn't look like I could play Jenga...
I've been able to develop a talent that I didn't have before.
That video is really good... and we can play Jenga.
Jenga. - Jenga. - Jenga.
Okay, I got it. Yay!
This is exactly the same.
It's exactly the same.
They're serving it to us.
I'll welcome you with a plate.
One more time, I had kamaboko. It smelled like a fishmonger's.
It was like a nice parley. It was fish.
Hiyoma had kamaboko this morning. She had it yesterday.
I went to get my hair cut yesterday.
It's long. Long.
I see. You've already cut it.
And changed the fringe.
It looks good.
Yeah, the bangs grew long recently.
So I cut it.
You know when people cut their hair?
Everyone gets long bangs?
It's about the same time as everyone else's.
When someone cuts it, I think it's nice.I thought it'd be nice to see someone else cutting it.
I've wanted to cut it off for a while.
But you know, for the coming-of-age ceremony, it's harder to arrange the hair if it's long.
I agree. It's nice. You still have some left over from the coming-of-age ceremony.
January.
I'll do something this year, too.
Wow, that's nice.
But I'd like to start with your friends.
We laughed, didn't we?
You're not smiling?
I'm gonna miss you.
I'm going to have dinner with my mom.
I'm only an adult now.
That's right.
Next time, we'll be friends.
I'll see you later.
Bye.
Ta-da!
Makeup is done.
My bangs aren't perfect yet.
Today.
I'm wearing twin tails in braids.
And me...
You know what I did?
I did a really big eyelash paring.
I did eyeliner.
And today
I'm going to eat sasakamama!
There was a big one, but I chose this one.
Bon appétit!
It's so good!
I can feel fish in my ears!
It's delicious!
Is it good?
I want to buy some pork cutlets.
Let's get some fish today!
I've got time.
We're close.
It won't be long.
Okay, let's go.
It's gonna be so refreshing.
You don't even know.
No, you didn't.
Good morning. - Good morning.
We're doing great today.
Absolutely.
What do you mean, you're not filming me?
I love the camera.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight.
And to all of you Darlamas out there, we're going to connect with your hearts.
We wish you a super happy birthday.
Happy Birthday to you.
Please, please, please, please.
Yes, yes, yes.yes, yes, yes.
Thank you for your hard work.
I hope you enjoyed this day...
I hope you enjoyed it.
I really...
Thank you very much.
I look forward to working with you again.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
Yes, sir.
When you wash your hands
I'll put this down before I wash my hands.
Yes, sir.
It's hot.
Perry Tan
And
Lactea Eagles Maipo
Paan
What a blah blah blah.
Take it home, everyone.
Something's not right.
Good night.
The staff's getting cold.
It's cold.
I'm so announcer-conscious.
My stomach hurts.
It won't go away.
Oh, God.
Oh, man.
Today is the Super Tokimeki Advertising Department Heart Rock On Hall Tour 2023
Thank you very much for coming!
I'm Haruka Koizumi, aka Oharu from Super Tokimeki Pink.
Before we begin, a few words of caution and a few requests from our guests, and then the show will begin shortly.
I love it.
Come on, let's get carried away.
Let's have fun in Sendai!
Date Masamune.
Okay, I'll be on my way.
junior junior hitoko tanomi haruka akin hiyori super-toki-meki hyoroshi hyoroshi hyoroshi hyoroshi hyoroshi hyoroshi hyoroshi hyoroshi hyoroshi
Rock and roll!
Hi everyone, I'll be there.
I'm going to go kamite member.
Please walk along the building.
This is the show.
Making it may have been a while since I've been here.
Funny.
Shimiiwakeya.
Shimi-iwake-ya.
Shimiwakeya.
Shimiwakeya.Shimi-wake-ya.
End with the second song.
Next time notice
Good night, Mr. *Ohkun*.
Atmosphere.
Open here and you'll find the advertising company.
There is a door here.
Very close, maybe.
With the advertising company.
It's time to say okay.
Oh, I heard that.
Yeah. - Yeah.
Aoo!!!
Thank you very much!
Bye bye Tsukushi's match.
Thank you!
I'm done with this.
Thank you very much for the contemporary performance!
[Applause]
Thank you for your hard work.
Absolutely not.
Yes! So today was the Sendai show!
It was so much fun.
It was hot, hot, hot.
There were one, two, and three rounds,
We could feel the aura of fun from all the performances,
It made us happy,
We were so happy to be hot.
There was a lot.
There were so many.
Yes, there were a lot. There were a lot of people.
It was a great venue.
What is it?
What?
Did you eat a lot of different kinds of beef tongue?
Hey!
In my stomach.
You ate beef tongue to comment on today's concert.
I was wondering what I was going to say about the show.
When am I going to say it? I wondered when I was going to say it.
I was just thinking about the piano and the fact that I ate beef tongue.
I was like, "I ate beef tongue.
I thought, "Well, people don't know about this.
I thought, "I'm going to tell them.
I thought it would be nice.
I want to tell Sene Mei.
I hadn't told you yet.
I came to Tokyo after eating.
Oh, that's right.
Beef tongue.
I went there to eat.
I ate beef tongue, too.
Hey. It was delicious.
Next time, let's go to Fukuoka.
Fukuoka!Fukuoka!
Fukuoka, Osaka, Tsuirei, Tsuirei. I thought you would say Tsuirei.
Say Tsuirei.
I will continue to do my best.
I will do my best.
So, thank you very much for Sendai.
I'll come again.
I'll be back.
Bye bye.
I'll see you soon.
I don't know why, but when I smile, the world seems to shine.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure somewhere someone's crying, somewhere I'll get my body wet again and not be cold.
Someone somewhere must be crying, because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them.
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future is painted, guiding me along
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the streets are turning colors
Now I can tell you the reason for my tears
Whenever you're lost, just remember
I'll smile even when it's raining
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools and sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are shimmering
My heart is like a sunny day, spilling clouds of tears
I'll wear a rainbow dress
LaLaLaLa...
Please subscribe to our channel!